Guide to the Women's Studies Program Reference Collection, 1988-ongoing
University Archives Duke University Durham, N.C., USA
Women's Studies Program Reference collection 1988-ongoing
University Archives, Duke University
Duke University. University Archives
0.5 Linear Feet approx. 350 Items
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Researchers must register and agree to copyright and privacy laws before using this collection.
All or portions of this collection may be housed off-site in Duke University's Library Service Center. The library may require up to 48 hours to retrieve these materials for research use.
Please contact Research Services staff before visiting the University Archives to use this collection.
Collection is open for research.
Provenance
The Women's Studies Program Reference Collection was compiled by University Archives from a variety of sources for use in reference and research.
Collection Overview
The Program in Women's Studies at Duke University is dedicated to exploring gender identities, relations, practices, theories and institutions. The collection includes clippings, flyers, newsletters, conference material, and program information.
Subject Headings
These are searchable subject entries for this collection. Performing a search on these subjects in the Duke University Libraries online catalog will bring up other related research materials.
Duke University. Women's Studies Program
Contents of Collection
- Container List
  - Awards (Box 1)
  - Graduate Program
  - Faculty Directory, 1988
  - History, 1993-1998 (2 folders)
  - House Courses
  - Report, The Impact of Women's Studies, 1995 (A95-107)
  - Friends Newsletter, 1988-1992
  - Calendar "Focus," 1986/87-1994
  - Engendering Knowledge/Engendering Power, 3rd Annual Women's Studies Graduate Research Conference, 1992
  - Feminist in Movement, 4th Annual Women's Studies Graduate Research Conference, 1993
  - Women's Works, Women's Words, 5th Annual Women's Studies Graduate Research Conference, 1994
  - Bodies of Knowledge, 6th Annual Women's Studies Graduate Research Conference, 1995
  - Inroads: Women and Gender Across the Academic Landscape, 7th Annual Women's Studies Graduate Conference, 1997
  - Clippings and Flyers
  - "Women's Studies at Duke University," [newsletter], 1990-2001 and "Proceedings" from the sesquicentennial symposium, 1989 March 3-5
  - Newsletters, copy 2